// import shuffleArray from "../helpers/shuffleArray.js";

// import { getRandomItem } from "../helpers/shuffleAnswer.js";
// const getRandomItem = (array) =>
//   array[Math.floor(Math.random() * array.length)];

// const shuffleArray = (array) => {
//   const shuffled = [...array];
//   for (let i = shuffled.length - 1; i > 0; i--) {
//     const j = Math.floor(Math.random() * (i + 1));
//     [shuffled[i], shuffled[j]] = [shuffled[j], shuffled[i]];
//   }
//   return shuffled;
// };

export const CaddyshackMovieQuestions = [
  {
    question: "Who directed the original Caddyshack movie?",
    options: ["Harold Ramis", "Ivan Reitman", "John Landis", "Bill Murray"],
    correctAnswer: "Harold Ramis",
  },
  {
    question: "What year was the original Caddyshack released?",
    options: ["1978", "1980", "1982", "1984"],
    correctAnswer: "1980",
  },
  {
    question: "Which actor played Carl Spackler in Caddyshack?",
    options: ["Chevy Chase", "Rodney Dangerfield", "Bill Murray", "Ted Knight"],
    correctAnswer: "Bill Murray",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the country club in Caddyshack?",
    options: ["Bushwood", "Pinehurst", "Augusta", "Pebble Beach"],
    correctAnswer: "Bushwood",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What animal does Carl Spackler obsessively try to catch throughout the movie?",
    options: ["Squirrel", "Gopher", "Rabbit", "Mole"],
    correctAnswer: "Gopher",
  },
  {
    question: "Who played Judge Elihu Smails in Caddyshack?",
    options: [
      "Ted Knight",
      "Rodney Dangerfield",
      "Chevy Chase",
      "Michael O'Keefe",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Ted Knight",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of Chevy Chase's character in Caddyshack?",
    options: ["Ty Webb", "Al Czervik", "Danny Noonan", "Lou Loomis"],
    correctAnswer: "Ty Webb",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which actor played Al Czervik, the loud and obnoxious newcomer to the club?",
    options: ["Bill Murray", "Chevy Chase", "Rodney Dangerfield", "Ted Knight"],
    correctAnswer: "Rodney Dangerfield",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the caddy who is the main character in Caddyshack?",
    options: [
      "Danny Noonan",
      "Tony D'Annunzio",
      "Maggie O'Hooligan",
      "Spaulding Smails",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Danny Noonan",
  },
  {
    question: "What song plays during the famous pool scene in Caddyshack?",
    options: [
      "I'm Alright",
      "Stayin' Alive",
      "Celebration",
      "Don't Stop Believin'",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "I'm Alright",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who performed the song 'I'm Alright' for the Caddyshack soundtrack?",
    options: ["Kenny Loggins", "Huey Lewis", "Billy Joel", "Elton John"],
    correctAnswer: "Kenny Loggins",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What does Carl Spackler claim to have received for total consciousness on his deathbed from the Dalai Lama?",
    options: [
      "A million dollars",
      "Eternal life",
      "A golf club",
      "So he's got that going for him",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "So he's got that going for him",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What type of candy bar causes the pool evacuation in Caddyshack?",
    options: ["Baby Ruth", "Snickers", "Milky Way", "3 Musketeers"],
    correctAnswer: "Baby Ruth",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of Judge Smails' grandson in Caddyshack?",
    options: ["Spaulding", "Timmy", "Bobby", "Junior"],
    correctAnswer: "Spaulding",
  },
  {
    question: "What does Al Czervik's golf bag feature?",
    options: ["A built-in bar", "A TV", "A stereo", "All of the above"],
    correctAnswer: "All of the above",
  },
  {
    question: "What is Carl Spackler's job at Bushwood Country Club?",
    options: ["Groundskeeper", "Caddy", "Golf Pro", "Bartender"],
    correctAnswer: "Groundskeeper",
  },
  {
    question: "What does Ty Webb use to putt while blindfolded?",
    options: ["A rake", "A pool cue", "A baseball bat", "A shovel"],
    correctAnswer: "A rake",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the scholarship Danny Noonan is trying to win?",
    options: [
      "Smails Scholarship",
      "Bushwood Scholarship",
      "Caddyshack Scholarship",
      "Golf Caddy Scholarship",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Smails Scholarship",
  },
  {
    question: "What does Carl Spackler use to try to kill the gopher?",
    options: ["Dynamite", "Poison", "A rifle", "All of the above"],
    correctAnswer: "All of the above",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is Al Czervik's catchphrase when he's about to say something insulting?",
    options: [
      "Oh boy",
      "Hey everybody",
      "Get a load of this",
      "Did you hear the one about",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Hey everybody",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What sport does Lacey Underall excel at, according to her introduction?",
    options: ["Tennis", "Golf", "Swimming", "Horseback riding"],
    correctAnswer: "Swimming",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What does Judge Smails give his grandson Spaulding for his birthday?",
    options: ["A putter", "A hat", "A golf ball", "A set of golf clubs"],
    correctAnswer: "A putter",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What does Carl Spackler claim to have been during the Dalai Lama story?",
    options: ["A golf pro", "A caddy", "A greenskeeper", "A looper"],
    correctAnswer: "A looper",
  },
  {
    question: "What does Ty Webb say he doesn't believe in keeping score?",
    options: ["In life", "In golf", "In love", "In business"],
    correctAnswer: "In golf",
  },
  {
    question: "What does Al Czervik call Judge Smails?",
    options: ["Judge Schmails", "Your Honor", "Old Timer", "Pops"],
    correctAnswer: "Judge Schmails",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the boat that Al Czervik brings to the yacht club?",
    options: [
      "The Flying Wasp",
      "The Sea Serpent",
      "The Seafood Platter",
      "The Nautilass",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "The Flying Wasp",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What does Carl Spackler use as camouflage when hunting the gopher?",
    options: ["Bushes", "Grass", "Flowers", "A tree costume"],
    correctAnswer: "Bushes",
  },
  {
    question: "What game is Ty Webb playing when he first meets Danny Noonan?",
    options: ["Golf", "Darts", "Pool", "Chess"],
    correctAnswer: "Golf",
  },
  {
    question: "What does Judge Smails say will 'make you a man'?",
    options: ["Golf", "The Army", "College", "Hard work"],
    correctAnswer: "The Army",
  },
  {
    question: "What does Al Czervik accidentally do to Judge Smails' boat?",
    options: ["Sink it", "Crash into it", "Paint it", "Steal it"],
    correctAnswer: "Sink it",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What does Carl Spackler call his homemade explosive used against the gopher?",
    options: [
      "Gopher Bomb",
      "C-4 Plastic Explosive",
      "Shaped Charge",
      "Nitroglycerine",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "C-4 Plastic Explosive",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the actor who played Danny Noonan?",
    options: [
      "Michael O'Keefe",
      "Scott Colomby",
      "Brian Doyle-Murray",
      "John F. Barmon Jr.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Michael O'Keefe",
  },
  {
    question: "What does Ty Webb tell Danny is the key to better golf?",
    options: [
      "Be the ball",
      "Practice more",
      "Get better clubs",
      "Take lessons",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Be the ball",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the actress who played Lacey Underall?",
    options: [
      "Cindy Morgan",
      "Sarah Holcomb",
      "Chevy Chase's wife",
      "Bill Murray's sister",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Cindy Morgan",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What does Judge Smails always demand when he enters the clubhouse?",
    options: ["A vodka martini", "His mail", "His golf clubs", "Silence"],
    correctAnswer: "His mail",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is Carl Spackler's proposed fee for killing all the golfers?",
    options: [
      "A million dollars",
      "Free golf for life",
      "Fifty thousand dollars",
      "A hundred and fifty thousand dollars",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "A hundred and fifty thousand dollars",
  },
  {
    question: "What does Al Czervik offer to bet on the big golf match?",
    options: ["$20,000", "$50,000", "$80,000", "$100,000"],
    correctAnswer: "$80,000",
  },
  {
    question: "What does Ty Webb say he was born to do instead of work?",
    options: ["Play", "Golf", "Relax", "Party"],
    correctAnswer: "Play",
  },
  {
    question: "What does Carl Spackler claim to have invented?",
    options: [
      "A new kind of grass",
      "A gopher trap",
      "A golf club",
      "A new putting technique",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "A new kind of grass",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the bishop who gets struck by lightning while golfing?",
    options: [
      "Bishop Pickering",
      "Bishop O'Hara",
      "Bishop Smails",
      "Bishop Czervik",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Bishop Pickering",
  },
  {
    question: "What does Al Czervik call his enormous golf bag?",
    options: ["The Monstrosity", "The Beast", "The Cadillac", "The Big Bertha"],
    correctAnswer: "The Monstrosity",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What does Judge Smails say Danny Noonan will 'get nothing and like it'?",
    options: [
      "And like it",
      "And be happy",
      "And be grateful",
      "And say thank you",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "And like it",
  },
  {
    question: "What does Carl Spackler claim the Dalai Lama said to him?",
    options: ["Gunga galunga", "Namaste", "Om shanti", "Jai guru deva"],
    correctAnswer: "Gunga galunga",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the caddy shack where Danny and the other caddies hang out?",
    options: ["The Shed", "The Hut", "The Shack", "The Clubhouse"],
    correctAnswer: "The Shed",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What does Ty Webb use to demonstrate his 'be the ball' philosophy to Danny?",
    options: ["A blindfold", "Earplugs", "A meditation technique", "Hypnosis"],
    correctAnswer: "A blindfold",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the tournament held at Bushwood Country Club?",
    options: [
      "The Bushwood Open",
      "The Smails Invitational",
      "The Caddyshack Classic",
      "The Club Championship",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "The Club Championship",
  },
  {
    question: "What does Al Czervik say 'looks good on you' to Judge Smails?",
    options: ["Orange balls", "That hat", "Those pants", "That shirt"],
    correctAnswer: "Orange balls",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What does Carl Spackler say he has to do to kill all the golfers?",
    options: [
      "Call the office",
      "Get some supplies",
      "Talk to his boss",
      "Get some help",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Call the office",
  },
  {
    question: "What does Ty Webb claim is in the bag that he gives to Danny?",
    options: ["Immortality", "Happiness", "Success", "Wealth"],
    correctAnswer: "Immortality",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What does Judge Smails yell when he realizes his boat is sinking?",
    options: ["My boat!", "Help!", "Czervik!", "Oh no!"],
    correctAnswer: "My boat!",
  },
];

export default CaddyshackMovieQuestions;
